http://ksmuseums.org/privacy/

Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed
this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use,
communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The
following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will
identify the purposes for which
information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the
objective of fulfilling those
purposes specified by us and for
other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the
individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for
the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and,
where appropriate, with the
knowledge or consent of the individual
concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to
be used, and, to the extent
necessary for those purposes, should be
accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security
safeguards against loss or theft, as
well as unauthorized access,
disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose personal information to
third parties who want to
market products to you, period.
We will make readily available to customers information about our
policies and practices relating to the management of personal
information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these
principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal
information is protected and maintained.
Follow:
2021 ConferenceThe 2021 KMA Conference will be held in Lawrence in early November 2021.
Check back for more information as it becomes available.Social Justice and Racial Equity Resources
Looking for social justice and racial equity resources for museums, staff, boards, and volunteers?
The page has moved to its new home under our
Resources menu.
Coronavirus Resources
Looking for coronavirus resources for museums?  The page has moved to its new home under our Resources menu.
Membership ApplicationJoin the Kansas Museums Association.
Join online using this link, where you can use a credit card or request an invoice:
KMA Memberships 2021
or
Join via mail by downloading:
Membership Form
Mail completed form with payment to:
Wichita State University
Public Policy and Management Center (Box 211)
Attn: KMA
1845 Fairmount
Wichita, KS 67260ContributionsKansas Museums Association (KMA) is a Section 501(c)(3) non-profit organization. Your contributions help support the programs.
Address Kansas Museums Association
Wichita State University
Public Policy and Management Center (Box 211)
Attn: KMA
1845 Fairmount
Wichita, KS 67260
Phone: 316.978.6535 (Morgan with KMA at WSU)
